keywordtooldominator.com 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy - Keyword Tool Dominator

The Website Owner, including subsidiaries and affiliates ("Website" or "Website Owner" or "we" or "us" or "our") provides the information contained on this website or any of the pages comprising the website ("website") to visitors ("visitors") (cumulatively referred to as "you" or "your" hereinafter) subject to the terms of service set out in this website's terms of service, the privacy policy and any other relevant terms of service, policies and notices which may be applicable to a specific section or module of this website. 

1\. Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

2\. The Information We Collect

When filling out a form, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address, which will not be shared with any party. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

We do not collect any sensitive or personal information including personally identifiable information, financial and payment information, or health information. 

If a visitor creates an account on our website, we do store authentication information including a visitor's user name, email address, and password. The password is encrypted using modern cryptography techniques and only the visitor can reset or change their password via our reset password process. 

We collect visitor tracking statistics using Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

We collect keyword tool usage statistics to help us analyze how our visitors are using the keyword tools. The information collected includes your IP address associated with a keyword tool. 

**Keyword Tool Dominator Google Chrome Extension**  
We do not collect or transmit any personal information, browsing data, and or sensitive user data through the extension. Data obtained from a web request is never collected, but only diplayed to the visitor and can be downloaded at the visitor's discretion. 

3\. Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

4\. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
